hearstcorp.com 2009-08-10

# Privacy Policy

** Privacy Policy ******

_Purpose of this Privacy Policy_

This privacy policy describes The Hearst Corporation's ("THC") policies with respect to the collection of personally identifiable information from the website to which this policy is linked. The website to which this policy applies is the home page, and related pages, of THC's corporate website, operating under the url "hearst.com". THC is one of the world's largest diversified communications companies, with interests in newspapers, magazines, broadcast and cable television, and a variety of other interests that are described on this website. 

_Information To Which This Privacy Policy Does Not Apply_

This privacy policy only applies to the web site operating under the url "hearst.com" (and the underlying pages that operate under that primary url) to which this policy is linked. Any information you provide when you a visit web site other than that covered by this policy (including other web sites affiliated with Hearst and its newspapers, magazines, and other publications such as for example, "hearstmags.com" (where you may purchase subscriptions to our magazines) or "hearstent.com") is subject to the privacy policies posted on those websites, whether such websites are run and owned by subsidiaries or affiliates of THC or by third parties. This policy also does not apply to information you may provide to us offline. 

_What is Personally Identifiable Information_

"Personally identifiable information" is information that can be used to identify you as an individual. Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, telephone number and any other information that is connected with you personally. 

_No Personally Identifiable Information Collected_

Hearst.com does not collect any personally identifiable information on this site, with the following exception. If you are an advertising agency or potential advertiser in certain of our magazines, you may make an online request to receive our media kit. In that event, we may collect information about your firm through an online registration process, and use that information to service your transactions with use and to send you promotional announcements. 

_Cookies_

Hearst.com (or third party service providers on our behalf) may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Hearst uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. 

Our cookies contain no personally identifiable information. 

Hearst.com (or third party service providers on our behalf) may also use cookies to collect aggregate information about web site users on an anonymous basis. We may share aggregate demographic and usage information with our prospective and actual business partners, advertisers and other third parties for any business purpose. 

If you don't want cookies, most Web browsers include an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of our sites may not function efficiently. 

_Non-US Users_

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using this website, you consent to this transfer. You also consent to the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with this website in the federal and state courts of, and in accordance with the laws of, the state of the United States in which the editorial staff of this website primarily does business. 

_California & Canadian Users_

California and Canadian users have certain rights to know how their personal information may be shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. The websites maintained by Hearst's publications and affiliates post information about their data sharing practices, and how you can elect to opt-out of certain data sharing arrangements. Please check the website associated with the applicable publication or affiliate for more information. 

_IP Address_

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, gather broad demographic information, and administer our website. 

_Changes to Privacy Policy and Notice_

THC may change this policy from time to time in its discretion. Your continued use of this site indicates your consent to this privacy policy and any amended versions of it. 

This policy was last updated on January 15, 2008.
